pakistanaffairs.pk 2014-11-29

# Privacy Policy - Important

  1. 2nd November 2012, 14:14 [#1](http://www.pakistanaffairs.pk/threads/7548-Privacy-Policy-Important?p=48309&viewfull=1#post48309)

> Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
>     * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
>     * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
>     * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
>     * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
>     * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
>     * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
>     * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 
>   
>  We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.  
>  **We use cookies on our website. By using our website you agree to this Policy and you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this Policy.**  
>  **About Cookies**
> 
> A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
>  There are two main kinds of cookies: “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies. Session cookies only last for the duration of users using the website and are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies outlast user sessions and remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.
> 
> * * *
> 
> **Cookies on this Website**
> 
> We use Session Cookies and Persistent Cookies on this website.  
>  **We use cookies for the following purposes:**
> 
>     * to improve the website’s usability
>     * to administer this website 
>   
>  Generally, we use cookies to help us administer this website, and to improve the website’s usability. Our Content Management System sets a cookie at the beginning of each visit to the site. This is primarily for administrative users, to enable them to login and modify and add content. It also gives us an indication of how many visits a particular page receives. The data is anonymous, and does not track your progress through the site. When leaving the site, the cookie is deleted.  
>  **Cookies do not contain any information that personally identifies you, a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you.**  
>  We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
>  You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.  
> 
> 
> * * *
> 
> **Third Party Cookies**
> 
> We also use third party cookies.  
>  Third party cookies may be used for the following purposes:
> 
>     * Our ‘Social Sharing’ Module uses **AddThis** , which enables you to share pages across Twitter and Facebook. **AddThis** uses cookies to enable you to link your social media accounts to the sharing function. [You can find out about AddThis’ Privacy Policy here](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy#.T-Gl77VYuQw).
>     * As part of our ‘Social Sharing’ Module, we use **Pinterest** , which enables you to Pin items of interest to **Pinterest Boards**. **Pinterest** uses cookies to identify you if you are a **Pinterest** user. [You can find out about Pinterest’s Privacy Policy here](http://www.spacecentre.co.uk/%20http:/pinterest.com/about/privacy/).
>     * In the [Blog](http://www.vbskinstudio.com/blog/) Section of the Site, we use **Disqus** , a hosted comments board. **Disqus** uses Cookies to identify you as a user, if you have a **Disqus** profile, enabling you to post comments and questions. [You can find out about Disqus’ Privacy Policy here](http://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy). 
>   
>  In addition, we use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at [www.google.com/privacypolicy.html](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html).  
>  Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. You can find out more about how cookies work, and how to manage them at [allaboutcookies.org](http://allaboutcookies.org/)  
>  This website cookies policy template is based on a free document supplied by The Legal Stop Limited through its website [www.thelegalstop.co.uk](http://www.thelegalstop.co.uk/)

* * *

#### Similar Threads

  1. Replies: 111 

Last Post: 21st September 2012, 08:37

  2. Replies: 33 

Last Post: 13th August 2012, 11:27

  3. Replies: 0 

Last Post: 12th August 2012, 10:31

  4. Replies: 0 

Last Post: 12th July 2012, 04:32

  5. Replies: 0 

Last Post: 2nd July 2012, 15:29

####  [](http://www.pakistanaffairs.pk/threads/7548-Privacy-Policy-Important#top) Posting Permissions 

  * You **may not** post new threads
  * You **may not** post replies
  * You **may not** post attachments
  * You **may not** edit your posts
  *
